I first met The Roots in 2004 when I was Amanda Diva, the host of Sucker Free Sunday on MTV2.
Hey, welcome back. It's me and I'll be so sure.
I gotta ask you something.
What's up?
Now, is that your real last name?
No, but you know, everybody calls me.
It's cool though. I like it. I like it.
Thanks to their late manager, Rich Nichols, rest in peace, I hosted The Roots Picnic for several years.
We're here at The Roots Picnic.
Next up, we got J. Period and Black Thought Live mixtape and Mobb Deep.
It's performing!
I DJed The Roots Picnic.
I even painted at The Roots Picnic.
I started my music journey around the same time Black Thought brought back the legendary Black Lily Festival.
It had birthed voices like Jill Scott and Bahamidea.
And as Amanda Diva, I was honored to now be in the lineage.
And I got to perform my version of A Change Gonna Come.
Are y'all ready?
And the change is coming right now.
Now it's 2026 and I'm reclaiming my timeline as Amanda Diva 2.0.
My new album, Truth Translator, drops June 14th.
It's not a movement.
It's movement music.